{
    "subject": "resource/Bridal_Veil,_Oregon",
    "predicate": "ontology/areaCode",
    "object": "503/971",
    "human_readable": "The area code of Bridal Veil, Oregon is 503/971.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9582882523536682,
            "question": "What is the area code for Bridal Veil, Oregon?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9492472410202026,
            "question": "Is 503/971 an area code used in Oregon?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9415794014930725,
            "question": "Which area codes serve Bridal Veil, Oregon?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9253753423690796,
            "question": "Can you call Bridal Veil using 503 or 971?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7157706022262573,
            "question": "Is there more than one area code used in Bridal Veil?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6139136552810669,
            "question": "What area code would you use to call a business in Bridal Veil?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5765239000320435,
            "question": "What state is Bridal Veil located in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5595631003379822,
            "question": "How can I find the area code for a specific location in Oregon?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4763442575931549,
            "question": "Do all areas within Oregon share the same area code?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4570949375629425,
            "question": "If you're calling Bridal Veil, what should your phone number look like?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The area code of Bridal Veil, Oregon is 503/971.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1789_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Do all areas within Oregon share the same area code?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1789_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How can I find the area code for a specific location in Oregon?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1789_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What state is Bridal Veil located in?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1789_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1789_114.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1789_126.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1789_139.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1789_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1789_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1789_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1789_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1789_84.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1789_86.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1789_99.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Based on the provided context information, I can evaluate the triple \"The area code of Bridal Veil, Oregon is 503/971.\" as follows:\n\n* The documents mention that Bridal Veil, OR is officially utilizing an area code overlay in which area codes 503 and 971 serve the same geographic area. (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_1789/re-ranker-msmarco/3.txt)\n* The documents also mention that the Zip Code Listing for Bridal Veil, Oregon is 97010 with an area code of 503. (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_1789/re-ranker-msmarco/86.txt)\n\nTherefore, the information in the documents supports the triple \"The area code of Bridal Veil, Oregon is 503/971.\"\n\nThe final answer is:\n```\n{\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\"output\": \"yes\"}\n```\n\nThe context information provided states that \"Bridal Veil, OR is officially utilizing an area code overlay in which area codes 503 and 971 serve the same geographic area.\" This supports the statement that the area code of Bridal Veil, Oregon is 503/971."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {'output': 'yes'}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}